Hello and welcome to your favorite
program, 'Rich and Famous.'
Where we introduce you
to rich and famous people.
Today we'll meet famous
industrialist and..
..owner of Malhotra group of industries,
Mr. Kailash Nath Malhotra.
Come on, I'll take you to
his splendid bungalow near Delhi.
Let me introduce you to Mr.
Kailash Nath Malhotra.
Greetings.
We want to know things about you
which the world has no idea about.
I'll tell you only if
it's worth telling to everyone.
Okay. First of all we
want to know about your family.
I have a big family.
I have a son, daughter-in-law.
I have a grandson and a
few relatives who stay with us.
I'll introduce them to you.
Come on.
Yes, me too!
Sit.
This is my son Ranjeet.
Hello. - Greetings.
This is my daughter-in-law Asha.
Hello. - Hello.
He is Ranjeet's brother-in-law,
Pankaj. - Hello!
His wife, Kanchan.
Hello! - Okay.
The rest is my staff.
Greetings!
Mr. Malhotra, generally there
are differences in a joint family.
What is secret of the peace
and joy your family enjoys?
It is simple.
My son runs the business and
his brother-in-law helps him out.
My daughter-in-law manages
the house with Kanchan's help.
And.. - I manage all of them.
I mean I do all the work
in the house making calls.
I have influential contacts.
I know all the central
ministers and secretaries.
He's right.
If a TV set stops working,
he doesn't call a mechanic..
..but the minister for
information and broadcasting.
He is Pappu.
Son of our accountant.
He grew up in our
house since childhood.
He is like my son. - Yes.
If you have any work
with any minister.
I'll get it done in a moment!
Please don't misunderstand.
This is his habit.
I see! - He's right.
What's the matter? Is a shooting
going on here for a soap opera?
We were missing the villain!
Welcome, sit down.
This is Dr. Balraj. - Hello.
He's my childhood friend
but he's no less than an enemy.
He has rationed my intake
of butter, salt and sugar.
He has even appointed
Pappu to spy on me.
If I had not done that,
you'd be chatting with god by now.
With so many diseases..
- What are you doing?
The camera is rolling.
- I'm sorry.
All right. Yes, is my pose okay?
All right, Mr.
Malhotra, one last question.
Your family is so happy.
Your life is so successful.
Is there any wish now which
you are waiting to get fulfilled?
Yes, I'm waiting for a companion.
Are you thinking
of marriage at this age?
Marriage!?
No. I'm waiting
for my great grandson.
The one who would be my toy.
He'll be my support
instead of this stick.
He'll carry forward
my family's name.
So sweet!
When is your wait going to end?
When my grandson,
Raj, agrees to get married.
Presently he's attending
his friend's wedding.
You look very beautiful.
Please! No! - Go on.
Move back.
Come on.
Enough.
What is this, brother-in-law?
You cannot go.
What is this?
What is it?
Go and dance!
Thank you.
You're one up on the boys!
- Really?
Yes.
Excuse me. - Yes?
You danced very well
at the function today.
You were saying something?
Your baby is very cute.
He has taken after you.
Thank you. Everyone says the same.
No, baby.
Okay. - Bye.
Bye.
Sister-in-law, take your son.
What was he saying? - Him?
Yes. - He said
my son is very cute.
He has taken after me.
He thought this baby is mine.
Chhotu! - Yes.
There's no running water.
- What are you saying
Yes. - What is happening here?
You're not working you lazy bums!
You're gossiping!
- Pappu, we're not gossiping.
There's no running water.
It's blocked.
You cut the grass!
No running water?
Paps. - Raj!
Who are you calling up? - I'm
calling the irrigation minister.
Why? - There's no running water!
Call the plumber. - Why call
the plumber for small repair work?
Is the irrigation minister
just for irritation?
Correct. - Correct!
Okay.
Only he recognizes
my talent in the family.
Water!
What's going on?
Saw that! Just dialing
the number has brought the water.
This is called power!
The water stopped again!
Pappu! - Yes.
The water has stopped. - Am
I your servant to call so often?
Take that!
Mom. - Raj!
My son has arrived.
How are you, dear? - I'm fine.
How was your friend's marriage?
- His life has totally changed.
Your life will also change.
Just say yes to marriage!
Sister is right.
You should get married.
I'm not going to
get trapped so soon.
Heard that! - Welcome home, Raj!
How are you, son?
Dad! - Live long.
How was your trip? - First class.
Good that you're here.
Do one thing.
Go to Singapore at once.
Find out why our ship
has not left from there yet?
The dealers here are pestering me.
Businessman!
What kind of a father are you?
The son has just arrived
and you're sending him out again!
You're always sending
this poor boy abroad. - Dad..
..we have to send someone.
- Then send someone else.
Pankaj, you go.
Then who'll handle the work here?
Have you brought the stuff? - Yes.
Come on! - What if we get caught..
Why are you scared? The
one who gets caught is the thief.
Sign language between
grandpa and grandson.
Something is surely wrong.
Come on, give me the stuff.
Grandpa, just one. - Of course!
Wow, sweets!
Sweet like your love
and soft like my heart.
Don't recite poetry. Eat quickly.
It's a risky affair.
You may close all doors
but I have the master key.
What is happening here? -
Sweets are being eaten in secret.
You have high diabetes. - Of 320!
Dad, it's a sin for
you to have sweets!
You take the medicines
and then the sweets too!
I get scolded for
eating the sweets. - Yes.
Dad, at least think about
us if not about your self.
Enough of it!
All of you are after a weak,
sick old man.
First ask,
why I have sent for sweets?
Why have you asked for sweets?
Why? - Raj has agreed.
Agreed?
For what? - For marriage!
What are you doing?
He is tired. Let him rest.
Let me talk to him.
I'll tell you everything.
Take these sweets
and celebrate. Go on!
What kind of a grandpa
are you? - Why?
You got me trapped
to save yourself.
What kind of a grandson are you?
Grandsons even give up their lives
to save their grandpa's honour.
You can't even
agree to get married.
Son, how will the Malhotra family
grow if you don't get married?
Ours is a very close knit family,
isn't it? - Yes.
There's so much love.
One wrong girl comes and
everything will go haywire.
Do you think I'll
get you an ordinary girl?
Still, I don't want
to get married. I'm sorry.
Sorry?
I'm also your grandpa!
I'll see to it
that you get married!
I'm also your grandson. Let go.
Open your mouth.
This doesn't mean I've
agreed to get married.
These sweets are
sugar free. Enjoy!
Good morning, sir. - Good morning.
Please sit. - Good morning, sir.
- Good morning.
Ms. Barucha! - Hi, handsome!
You look wonderful today.
- How many times have I told you?
Yes, if I had been married,
I'd be having two kids.
I'm still unmarried.
That's okay. Even I'm single.
And listen!
Until I find a good
and handsome boy like you,
I won't get married!
You shouldn't.
Okay? - Okay!
Hello. - Raj, this is Dr.
Balraj speaking.
Yes, doctor.
Come to my nursing home immediately.
Your grandpa is a little sick.
Not little, but very much!
He's very sick!
He was fine this morning. - One can't
guarantee health at this age.
It can deteriorate any time.
All right, I'm coming. - Okay.
He's coming!
Hello? - Mom,
did doctor uncle call?
He was here.
He did grandpa's routine
check up and they went for a walk.
Why are you asking?
Nothing. Okay, bye.
Your acting should be realistic.
Don't worry, Kailash.
I used to win acting
competitions in college.
Grandpa! - Yes?
- Raj has arrived. Lie down.
Take this. - Come on..
Oh my god!
Your pulse is not getting
normal even after two injections.
What is bothering you so much?
You still have one
more year of life.
All wishes of a man
get fulfilled in a year.
What's the matter?
I will fulfill your wish.
I have only one wish.
I should see my great grandson.
Raj loves his freedom,
not his grandpa.
Open your eyes, Kailash.
Raj is here.
Raj, where are you?
I am here, grandpa. Wonderful!
You're wearing a suit
and lying on the hospital bed!
I had to lie down in an emergency.
You also had to act badly
in emergency. Isn't it?
Doctor, you too are a part of it?
- What could I do?
Your grandpa forced me into it.
Grandpa, why do you do all this?
You know how valuable
you are to me.
I am valuable, right?
When are you coming
to select a girl? Answer me.
Whenever you say.
Priya, I think they've come.
Welcome, Mr. Malhotra!
Greetings, Mr. Kapoor.
Mr. Kapoor,
this is my grandson Raj.
Hello. - Hello.
You know Pappu. - Yes.
He's my son.
Greetings. - Live long.
He's the same guy I
had met at Suman's wedding.
I sensed the entire situation
when I saw you two there.
That's why we've
asked for this alliance.
I have already seen and
chosen your daughter. - Yes.
I wanted Raj to meet her.
Come, daughter.
Hello. - Hello.
Live long. Sit.
Yes.
Do you like her?
Grandpa,
doesn't she look a bit old?
What are you saying?
I've seen her horoscope.
Her age is perfect.
It seems grandpa has seen
the horoscope without his glasses.
Her cheeks are so plump.
That's the sign of beauty.
Have you seen her smile?
She looks so cute.
The one beside her looks better.
She's a mother of a baby.
Then she looks like a mother of 4.
Doesn't she?
What are you saying?
She doesn't look like!
Son, ask her anything
if you want to.
Yes. Ask her anything.
What are you educational
qualifications?
Me?
I've studied till 7th class.
She's a double graduate.
She knows all household chores.
She had prepared all these
savories, snacks and sweets.
It means she doesn't
know anything.
She knows so much.
What else do you want?
Why is he asking me questions?
He's still looking at you.
Get ready. He'll ask you again.
What are your hobbies?
Badminton, cricket, tennis, swimming,
music are her main hobbies.
It's her habit to praise others.
She is in fact a gold
medalist in Kabaddi.
Kabaddi?
Dear, even I want
to ask you something.
What is the most important
thing that keeps a family happy?
Love.
If there is love among the family
members the home turns to heaven.
Wonderful!
She has such nice views.
What will we do with her views?
Ask her views.
Why do you want her
sister-in-law's views?
Sister-in-law? - Yes.
Quiet, dear.
Daughter-in-law,
your son was crying.
Take him. - Come!
Come, my son!
My pretty son!
Congratulations, Mr. Kapoor!
To you too. - Raj likes the girl!
The match is fixed from our side.
Fix the wedding date
as soon as possible.
Sure, why not.
Have some sweets. - Sure.
Priya.. - Raj..
Raj!
No, let her go. I'll hit you.
Search it, darling. Find the ring.
Doctor uncle, there is no difference
between love and photographs.
How? - Both are
developed in the dark.
Naughty guy!
Who has taken Raj's picture? Look!
Mom, I have taken this picture.
Raj had no clue I
was taking a picture.
It seems you two have
liked Switzerland a lot.
Why don't you two settle
down there for a few years?
Absolutely not!
They'll not go anywhere.
Now you want to send both son
and daughter-in-law abroad! No!
When I had sent you to Oxford
university, you had cried a lot.
Dad, you are..
Grandpa, you should have told me.
I'd have told the foreign minister
to open a branch of Oxford here.
Fool, you were not even born then.
That is the misfortune
of our country.
Raj, phone.
Hello?
All right. Hello, one second.
I'll call you later.
Whose call was it that
you had to go away and talk?
Raj, you are hiding something.
What's the matter?
You're right.
I thought I'd hide
this matter from you.
But such things can't be hidden.
What would you do if you knew..
..there's someone
else who share's my love?
I'll kill myself.
Raj, do you love someone else?
I don't.
I will start now. - What?
Doctor had called up.
The report is positive.
Priya, you're pregnant.
Raj!
What? I'm going to
be a great grandfather.
Have a long life!
Live long!
Bansi!
Yes! - Distribute
this among the poor.
Okay. - Daughter-in-law!
Asha! - Yes, dad.
Congratulations, daughter-in-law!
You're going to become a grandma!
I'll be a great grandpa!
I'm very happy today!
Chhotu!
God has heard my prayers.
Live long, dear.
Have a long life! - Ranjeet!
What is it, dad?
- You're going to get my position.
What? - You're going to be
a grandpa and me, a great grandpa.
Congratulations!
Pappu! - What?
I'll become a great uncle.
- I'll be great Pappu.
Grandpa, congratulations!
I've seen so much joy in this
house for the first time today.
All because of you.
Thank you. - Thanks to you.
Love you.
Kailash, congratulations!
Congratulations!
You'll remember me for this!
I've brought sweets today.
I'll have lots of it and
offer you too. - No, Balraj.
I won't have sweets anymore.
I want to live.
I don't need this stick.
My support is on his way!
I'll do everything
as you direct me to.
Cricket, tennis, jogging.
Chhotu, master is going
for a morning walk after years.
Without his stick!
This is daughter-in-law's magic.
I was very scared when I knew
I'd be married into your family.
Why?
I had seen your picture
in the newspapers.
I thought a person
with such big moustache..
..must be a dictator
and very strict.
I'd always have to put on a veil.
After coming here,
I found out you're very modern.
I feel you're not
Raj's but my grandpa.
Mom, this year we had a good crop
in our garden for the first time.
100 kilos of mangoes
have ripened on every tree!
Were you plucking
or weighing the mangoes?
Aunt, chocolate?
- Stop gossiping and do your work.
This will go to Mr.
Sharma. Put them in that basket.
Okay. - This is for Dr. Kumar.
Give it to me.
- Put it in that basket.
Take this. - What are you doing?
I have told you many times. Don't
lift heavy things in this condition.
Take out these raw mangoes.
Where had you been
early in the morning?
I went shopping. - For what?
Maharana Pratap's. - What?
I mean Maharana Pratap's
photograph. - Why?
Because a mother in
her 6th month of pregnancy..
..gets a baby with skills
of the one whom she sees the most.
If we hang Maharana
Pratap's picture..
..in Priya's room then the
baby will also be brave like him.
Have you gone crazy?
If the baby is like
Maharana Pratap..
..he'll be fighting
in jungles his entire life.
We should make
the baby a cricketer.
What will he do
by being a cricketer?
He'll uselessly get involved
in some match fixing.
We should make our
baby a politician..
..who can take the
entire country forward.
That's why in Priya's room..
What happened? Fallen asleep?
No, I'm thinking which politician's
photograph I should hang.
Shall I say something? - Go on.
Your problem can be solved.
- Really?
Hang a film hero's photograph
in daughter-in-law's room.
He can be a politician, a cricketer
and also Maharana Pratap.
Very simple!
It would've been better if you had
not spoken! Politician's photograph!
Maharana Pratap!
Sachin Tendulkar! - Politician!
Sachin Tendulkar!
- Why are you quarrelling?
Ask Priya whose picture
she wants to hang. - Yes!
Yes, dear, tell us.
Why are you worried about me?
I have already hung my
favorite photograph. - Whose?
Come on, brother!
Yes!
My god!
Four!
Ball please!
Come on, Pappu!
Pappu, well done!
Come on!
Buck-up, Pappu!
Come on, Pappu.
Very good! Come on!
My god!
Bansi, catch it! - Catch it!
I missed it!
Bansi, you fool!
You are out!
How can I be out, grandpa?
That was a six.
Decision's been given!
What is this?
Grandpa is cheating, mom.
It's not fair. - Not fair!
Boy, our family's rule is, the one
who crosses the boundary is out.
Give me the bat.
- So you want to bat?
Yes, I want to bat.
-Yes, you go bat.
I'll be the umpire. - You'll
be out on the very first ball.
Go on, you can't bowl me out!
Come on! - Come on, dad!
Hurry up! All the best, dad!
Come on bowl.
How's that? - Out!
You bowl so fast! It zoomed
past before I moved my bat!
I'm not out.
Tell him he's out.
Not out!
He's out! - What are you saying?
He is out! Dad is out!
Okay!
Out! - Yes!
You're not my friend
but a traitor.
What had we agreed upon?
What could I do? All of
them forced me to give you out.
What do you mean you were forced?
'Family match' fixing!
Very bad! I'll call the
sports minister and tell him now.
Forget it.
I won't bat. - It is my turn.
Yes, come on.
Everyone, take your positions.
Welcome, madam! - Thank you, dad!
Ready!
You don't know to play cricket and
you'll hang Tendulkar's photograph!
Now watch how I hit a six.
- Next ball.
Hit a six!
Bowl!
Six! -Come on, catch it! Catch it!
Priya!
Daughter-in-law!
Dear!
I don't understand anything.
It's been two hours. Why
are they not keeping us informed?
Balraj went in and
hasn't yet returned.
What happened, uncle?
Is everything okay?
Daughter-in-law had a miscarriage.
The baby passed away in the womb.
And Priya? - She is fine.
Out of danger.
Thank god,
my daughter-in-law is safe.
Can we meet Priya? - No,
we have drugged Priya to sleep.
It won't be right to
disturb her for 7-8 hours.
I think all of us should go home.
No one has rested since
this accident occurred.
Come on, let's go. - You all go.
I'll stay here.
No, aunt.
Both of us will stay here.
Mom, I'll stay here.
But son.. - As soon as Priya
regains consciousness, I'll call you.
Yes, come on, everybody.
Kailash, you too come.
Losing baby is a
great shock to a mother.
Take care of Priya.
- Yes, grandpa.
Mr. Malhotra,
the doctor has called for you.
I'll be right back. Okay?
Come, Raj. Sit.
Dear..
I have hidden
something from you all.
What?
Priya's uterus was
damaged in the accident.
It had become septic.
To prevent further
infection the doctor..
..had to remove her
uterus and ovaries.
Priya can never conceive
again due to this.
Even the most modern and latest
technology can't help her now.
You have to conceal this matter
from everyone in the family.
If your grandpa
comes to know of it.
He's already had
two heart attacks.
He can't survive one more.
How can I tell this to Priya..
It's okay.
There's only one way
to lend courage to the family.
That we don't show our sorrow.
Shall we?
The kids have come.
I need no crying or regrets.
Everyone will behave
as if nothing has happened.
Understand? - Yes.
Get on your routine.
Welcome, children.
Our daughter-in-law has a long life.
I thought of her and here she is.
Live long.
Daughter-in-law, you'll see.
Within a year,
we'll have a newborn in our house.
Priya!
Live long and have many children!
Enough.
No, Priya.
No, dear. Don't cry.
We shouldn't be sorry for
the one who was not even born.
Calm down, dear. - Miscarriage
is a very ordinary thing.
Even my friend had a miscarriage,
she now has 4 children.
4 children in the
age of family planning?
Pappu! - Yes?
Complain to the police
against her friend.
Police? I'll call the family planning
minister and have her arrested.
Her friend's husband
is the family minister.
How will you arrest her?
Call the prime minister!
Where can I find him?
Why are you laughing?
I can even call
up Bill Clinton. Yes!
What is happening?
Everyone is talking.
No one cares about daughter-in-law.
She has returned from the hospital.
Yes, Priya. Go and rest.
I'll prepare you
favorite food today.
Come, sister-in-law.
Bring the groceries, Pappu.
Of course. - Aren't you
going to office? - Yes, Pankaj.
Yes, there's so much work left.
- Daughter-in-law.
Go to your room and rest.
Raj, take her.
What happened?
Have you looked into the
eyes of your family members?
There's a hope in their eyes that
soon I'll give an heir to this house.
One day they will get to
know that we have cheated them.
What will happen then?
- Don't worry about that.
I've thought of something.
What do you think?
We'll adopt a small, cute baby.
Daddy always tells us to
go abroad to handle the business.
If you want, we'll go abroad
for a few years and adopt a child.
Okay?
I'll explain to doctor uncle.
What other option do we have?
Grandpa.
Come, dear.
Greetings. - Live long.
Come, sit.
Were you crying? - No.
These are tears of joy.
I dozed off reading
the newspaper..
..and had a pretty dream.
That I've become
a great grandfather.
I saw a small baby
playing on my lap giggling.
Exactly like Raj!
The same eyes, the same smile.
As soon as I lowered
my head to kiss him..
..the naughty boy
grabbed my moustache.
My eyes were filled
with tears of joy.
Early morning dream
always comes true.
Hail the lord!
Thank you, my love.
Raj! - Yes.
If I ask for something from you,
will you give it to me?
Why ask? Everything is yours.
What if I want to give
away that which is mine?
Go ahead. What's the problem?
You should remarry.
What? - Today grandpa saw a dream.
A small baby, just like you,
was playing on his lap.
He doesn't want someone
else's but your own child.
How can we play
with his sentiments..
..calling an adopted
baby as our own child?
Raj, I am infertile.
I can't become a mother
but you can be a father.
Please, Raj.
Would you remarry..
..if I had met
the same fate as you?
Look..
Everything is going to
be perfectly okay. I love you.
Yes, Priya.
- Raj, I want to meet you at once.
Why? What is it?
I can't tell you over the phone.
Do one thing.
I'll reach India gate.
You come there.
All right. I'll be there.
What is it?
Why did you call me here?
Read this news.
Surrogate mother!
The girl was lucky to have a child
even though she couldn't conceive.
The only difference was that
the womb belonged to someone else.
You mean a test tube baby!
No, our family is so famous that..
..the matter of a test
tube baby can't be hidden.
It means you want me to..
- Yes, Raj.
We should find a girl
who can give birth to our baby.
If I needed someone else
to give birth to my baby..
..why would I refuse to remarry?
Why would I talk
of adopting a child?
As I love you very much
and I don't want to share it.
You get sorrows for free but..
..you have to pay a price for joy.
I'm ready to share your love
with another woman for my child.
Priya, even if I listen to you,
where will we find such a girl?
If I am destined to be a mother,
we will find someone.
Hi, handsome!
The foreign marketing
deal we're doing..
..with your N.
R. I friend, Ajay Sharma..
'Will she help me?'
This is your air ticket to Mumbai.
What happened? You look disturbed.
Nothing, Ms. Barucha. Sit down.
There's a problem.
- Tell me your problem.
I'll solve your problem easily.
Ms. Barucha, this problem
won't get solved easily.
It will take at least nine months.
What? - Yes.
I have a friend who needs a girl.
- Really?
Is he handsome like you?
He is handsome and rich.
He is ready to give everything.
House, car, bungalow, everything.
All he needs is a baby.
Let the wedding take place.
I'll give him as many
children as he wants.
The problem is that
he is already married.
He doesn't want to remarry.
What? A child out of wedlock?
Is there a problem?
- What nonsense!
You have misunderstood me.
Am I a lowly girl?
Ms. Barucha,
you've misunderstood me!
I'm not that sort of a boy.
I was just discussing
my friend's problem with you.
To hell with your
friend and his problem!
My body and soul belongs
to my husband! Understand?
What idiot friends he
has who have such problems!
Thank you.
Congratulations, Raj.
Until now, we were just friends.
Now we're business partners.
Thank you.
Mrs. Kapoor. - Thank you, sir.
First of all, let me congratulate
Mr. Raj Malhotra and Mr. Ajay Sharma.
We're glad to announce that Mr.
Ajay Sharma's company..
..will market all of Mr.
Raj Malhotra's products in Europe.
I request Mr.
Raj Malhotra to tell us which..
..product should
be launched first..
'Will she help me? '
Mr. Raj,
I know about your problem.
I am ready to help you.
Thank you, you are very nice.
- It's my honour.
Priya will be very
happy to hear this.
Raj, Mrs. Kapoor is asking
your opinion about your product.
Sir, I was asking which
product to launch first.
I'm sorry. I was lost somewhere.
Can we discuss this
in the next meeting?
Sure. Why not?
I'm missing my wife
a bit too much today.
Excuse me, sorry. Bye.
See you later, brother. - Yes.
Where do you want to go?
- Straight ahead.
Turn left from here.
Stop here.
Your house is..
I can see nothing here.
Why do you need a house? Come on!
What!? - It's an AC car.
We'll have fun.
I charge rs.1000 for a night.
You can pay a little less. C'mon.
You've been mistaken.
I saw you and I gave you a lift.
I was about to drop you home.
Meaning? - I mean..
I have a different problem.
I have a friend. He needs a girl
who would stay with him for a year.
For a year?
Rascal! You are a wolf
under a sheep's skin.
This is your story
not your friend's, right?
Yes. - Look, Mister.
I have got two lives
to take care of.
They have no father to
look after them. So I can't come.
But there's a girl
who dances at Deepa Bar.
You should meet her.
Her name is Madhubala.
Your job will be done. Go on.
I'll call her up. - Thank you.
One second. Take this.
You haven't touched me,
yet you offer money.
This is not for you
but for your children.
I'll pray that
your work gets done.
Thank you.
Entice that rich guy.
You, want to have fun?
No.
Wait!
Madhubala, get me the money.
They showered money on you.
Where's the rest of it?
What are you talking about?
- You'd or should I help?
Don't touch. - C'mon, bring it.
Here!
Here's your commission.
Hey Mina! Get going!
I'm going. He's a jerk!
Come, dear.
Wonder where they come from!
I got a call from
Vyjanti that you'll come.
What's it?
Didn't she tell you?
Madhubala, coming?
C'mon get going!
You're throwing attitude today!
You'd mind leaving now!
Yes, boss?
We won't be able to talk here.
Shall we go somewhere else?
That's going to cost even more.
Alright.
Let's go.
Come.
Boss, why here?
Come to Chandni.
There are many customers there.
One gets everything that's
needed for free, besides the room.
My room's here.
Oh! - Come.
- Seem to be very rich!
Get to the lift. I'll get the key.
Good evening.
Why do these sandals get loose?
Damn it!
You fool!
Why are you showing your teeth?
Are they new? Fatso!
Shall we?
Good evening, sir. - Good evening.
Sir, don't tip him.
Madam is very generous.
Is it? He's very cunning.
Give him the tip.
Take. - Thank you, sir.
Fatso, half of it is mine. - Okay.
Come on.
What a big room!
I had heard big
hotels had big rooms.
Sir, this is so big.
They even have TV.
Is it yours?
- No, it belongs to the hotel.
Do you want to watch? - Yes.
Is this a mobile phone?
- No, this is remote control.
Madhubala!
I forgot.
- There is need for that.
Why? You're not in the right mood?
No, I want to talk to you.
You.. - I'll charge
you double for that.
I was just joking!
Sit down!
Now I don't need to
talk to you about price.
I take a lot of money when
I go out. I charge 700-800 rupees!
You brought me to a good place.
Spoke nicely.
You're handsome.
I'll charge you extra.
I'll take 1,000 rupees.
All right, how much
will you charge for a week?
3,000!
For a month?
Do you like me so much?
Even I like you a lot.
Okay, give me 15,000 for a month.
For a year? - A year!
That would be too much.
I'm not that good in math.
20,25,35.
That would be a 100,000!
How much is it?
200,000!
200,000!?
I haven't seen
so much money before.
Sir, I won't do anything kinky.
Don't worry, I am married
and I love my wife very much.
It shows.
We have everything.
We don't have a child.
I need a baby from you. - Baby?
Why? Can't your wife have babies?
I can't stop laughing!
Why did you come to me?
I need a baby from you.
I am ready to pay
whatever amount you ask.
How much can you pay?
Half a million! A million!
Hello?
Million! - What happened?
Are you okay? - A million!
What happened?
You will pay me a million
in return for a child?
Will you dump me after I conceive?
I can give you the money
right now. - I trust you.
What will the world
say if you give your wife..
..the baby of a
street girl like me?
The world will speak
only if it knows anything.
All right, everything in secret?
My hard earned money! Boss, it's amazing.
I used to earn for my stomach.
Now my stomach's
going to earn for me?!
Boss, I have only
one principle in life.
I never kiss on lips. Okay?
Okay.
A million!
Hello!
Priya! - Hi,
I was waiting for your call.
I have found a girl
who'll give you a baby.
Really?
Yes.
She must be an angel.
She must be a good
person to help us.
One million!
She is good.
Priya.. - I understand.
She is from a poor family, right?
Priya, she is..
It is enough if
she is well-cultured.
One million! Hi!
My hard earned money!
I love you, Priya.
- I love you too.
Bye.
Buy some good clothes
for yourself tomorrow.
Take this 50,000.
Buy clothes that cover your body.
Why? Don't you like my body?
Nice body! But keep it covered.
Okay.
Tell your family that
you'll be with me for a year.
I don't have anyone
in this world except you.
All right, go to sleep.
- Come on, I'm ready.
No, you sleep here.
I'll sleep there.
What?
You sleep here. I'll sleep there.
No! I need my million quickly!
No. - My million!
You'll get it. Go to sleep.
I don't know when I'll get it!
Oh god!
Excuse me. - How much for this?
It's not meant for you.
Speak in Hindi.
- It is not for you.
Why? Is the material
bad or the color?
It is expensive.
You can't afford it.
What are you saying?
Look I have money!
Come on, go out.
Why should I go out?
I have the money.
I have come to buy clothes.
- I told you once.
Go out. Please!
Get out!
How dare you scold me!
To hell with you!
Do you think I'm a lowly girl?
I can buy your entire shop!
Understand? - We neither want
to sell the shop nor the goods.
Only decent people come here.
Get out!
You scoundrel! Do these decent
people give you special money?
Watchman! - Yes, sir.
Don't touch me!
Do you think I'm that cheap?
You rascal! I won't spare you!
You have such a big shop
but have no manners at all.
The lowly rascal!
Move!
The scoundrel scolded me!
I won't spare the rascal!
He kicked me out of the shop!
He thinks every well
dressed person is decent!
Excuse me, madam. - What?
Where are you going? - Upstairs.
Why do you ask?
- I am the general manager.
Who do you want to meet?
- That sir!
Which sir?
- The fair guy with big eyes.
He brought me here last night.
His room is upstairs.
- Room number?
I don't know the number.
The room with a view of the ocean.
We have many rooms
with a view of the ocean.
Come with me.
I'll show you. - Excuse me, madam.
You can't go upstairs.
- Baldy, you are misbehaving now!
If he finds out, you'll be sacked.
Madam, you'll have to
get out of the hotel. Please.
Ladies like you can't
enter our hotel. Get out!
Let me go! - Come on. Out!
Let go of my hand. - That's all.
Hey fatso. Come here! - Good
morning, madam. - He knows me.
Tell this fool that you know me.
You know her? - Yes, sir.
Why wouldn't he?
He took me upstairs.
You?
Sir, she was with Raj Malhotra.
- Raj Malhotra?
Excuse me, madam.
I was not on duty last night.
That's why I made a mistake.
I'm quite sure you'll
forgive my small mistake.
I'm quite sure you won't tell Mr.
Raj about this.
Who is Mr. Raj? - Raj Malhotra!
The person that brought you here!
My young man's
name is Raj Malhotra?
Will you come with me? - No.
Let's go. What are you staring at?
Where is my young man?
Food for expecting mothers
will be the first product..
..to be launched in
the international market.
My friend and business partner,
Ajay Sharma..
..will promote it through
his American companies.
I'll provide him with all the..
..technical help he needs.
- Yes, thanks.
Mr. Sinha. - Yes, sir!
Our product has good
prospects in Europe's markets.
Sir!
Come here!
Excuse me.
Sir, the money you gave,
the shopkeeper said..
..he won't give clothes
to girls like me.
Go upstairs, I'm coming.
No, I'll eat with you.
Go upstairs and order.
Rascal, you can eat with
these loafers but can't offer me?
Who is she?
I am sorry. Please forgive me.
Sorry. - It's okay.
Please, Mr. Sinha. - Yes, sir.
In the market survey report..
Raj, who is she?
A friend.
That she is. Is she a call girl?
She's a good girl.
That she is,
but she's a call girl, right?
Who doesn't do business? You, me.
Everybody. - You're right.
Why did you come downstairs?
What was so important that you
had to disturb me at the meeting?
If you are ashamed of me,
why didn't you tell me before?
You could have locked
me in the bathroom.
Even that shopkeeper insulted me!
He said he won't sell
clothes to a girl like me.
Why are you staring like this?
I don't get angry with food.
If you want, take it.
- I don't need it.
Which shopkeeper? - That
big shopkeeper across the road.
What did he say? - I told you.
He disgraced me and now you too.
I am sorry. I forgot you've
come from another world.
I didn't come here.
You brought me into your world!
Use this.
Hold it.
Come with me. - Where?
To buy clothes
from that very shop.
I won't go there.
Madhubala.. Ms. Madhubala.
What happened? - For the
first time, someone talked so..
..respectfully to me.
Come on!
Let's go. Come.
Mr. Bhatia's bill..
You've come here again!
I've brought her here.
You.. - Raj Malhotra.
Raj Malhotra?
Mr. Malhotra! I can't believe it!
It's an honour that
you've come here to shop.
She has come here to shop.
She has come with you? Sure!
Jessy! Rita!
Seema! Attend to madam.
No, you will attend her. - Sure!
Come, madam.
Go, madam! - Please come!
Take this, madam. - No.
Have this drink, madam.
I've brought it for you.
Go through the dresses while I arrange
good shoes and sandals for you.
Kalpana, for madam.. - You get it!
Come on. Hurry up. - Yes!
Try this. Do you like this?
No?
Okay.
I had thought I'd
buy your entire shop.
Your shop contains
nothing which suits her.
Did you like anything? - No.
Shall we go to some
other big shop? Let's go.
Sorry. - You are hot tempered.
Have cold drink.
Old man!
- Don't do this in future.
Yes.
What are you doing?
- Smoking is injurious to health.
Even this.
- Sir, this is a small bottle.
A small bottle makes a large
hole in your liver. Give it to me.
Madhu, my wife shouldn't
know who you are.
Okay?
Okay.
What are you doing?
Are you going to make me bald?
It's okay. Don't worry.
Madhu! Priya!
Madhu! How will I repay your debt?
Forget it!
It's between two ladies.
Only a woman can understand
a woman's sorrow.
Was that good?
Very good. But be polite.
That is okay.
When will we meet Priya madam?
We're going to
Switzerland tomorrow.
You'll meet her at
Delhi airport. Okay?
Until then rehearse
it over and over.
Okay? - With love!
Only a woman can understand
a woman's sorrow.
Is that okay?
Bansi, hurry up or else they'll
miss the plane! - Yes, hurry up!
Live long.
Call me up and take care. - Yes.
All the best, son.
Have a good flight?
I have called our Zurich office.
The driver will come to receive you.
Yes. - All the best.
If the driver doesn't show up,
I'll call the pilot. - Dear, come here.
Take this sacred thread.
As soon as you conceive, put
it on. It will protect the baby.
Yes. - Live long.
Live long. Take care.
Don't worry.
I'll manage everything here. Okay?
Thank you, doctor.
- God bless you.
All right, Pappu. - Call
me if Raj doesn't look after you.
Live long, dear.
Take care of her. - Yes.
Best of luck. - Thank you.
Bye, son. - Shall we leave?
Bye. - Bye!
Bye. - Bye.
Raj, where is she?
I told her to meet here.
Priya!
Madhu.
Come.
Madhu, this is Priya.
Hi. - Hi.
I don't know what to tell you.
I can't even thank
you for such a big favor.
It's all right.
Only a woman can understand
a woman's sorrow.
Come, Madhu.
Hi, Priya! - Hi!
Oh my god!
This is my cousin and his wife.
Welcome to Switzerland, sister!
- Hi, brother Vicky.
How are you? - How are you?
Hello, Raj. How are you? - Nice to see you.
- Welcome to Switzerland.
Hello. - Hello.
This is Madhu.
She was with us in our flight.
She lives here. - All right.
I called your dad yesterday and
he said you're coming here today.
So I've come to pick you all up.
You guys have to stay in my house.
Last time you came for honeymoon
and I didn't disturb you.
You'll have to stay
with me this time.
We have to stay away
this time as well.
As the office is
close to the bungalow.
I have lots of work. - All right.
My baby's tonsure ceremony will
be held during a holy festival.
You two have to say
with us for a week.
You have to stay with us!
Come, I'll drop you.
- No, my car has arrived.
All right.
I'll drop you to the car. Come.
Please come.
Madhu, this is our house.
We'll stay here.
Wow! A house amidst the hills.
I am shaken after seeing this.
I've melted after seeing the snow!
And how's that?
Come on. Let's go out.
Teacher,
have you taught her all this?
I tried a little.
No problem.
I'll teach her the rest.
Madhu, come in.
What do you think of the house?
- It is very nice.
This is my room.
This is yours.
Madam!
Madam, this coat has got stuck.
- Let me take it out for you.
Call me Priya.
My god! How can I take your name?
The way I take yours.
There's no sir
or madam here. Okay?
My god! Such a big
swimming pool in your room!
You can swim whenever you want.
If you like it then you stay here.
I'll go to your room.
Okay? - Okay.
I'll get my luggage.
Madhu liked this room
so I gave it to her.
I'll stay in the guest room.
- It's okay.
We've already seen this room.
Let's see the guest room. - Come.
Not like this.
I'll take you to the guest room the
way I had brought you to this room.
This is my room.
The one there is yours.
I know. But my wife is here.
You belong to me. Don't you?
Oh god!
Fruit, vegetables, groceries,
clothes, shoes, all in one shop.
Yes. Madhu,
take whatever you want.
Yes.
Wine shop!
Attention please.
Since there's a weather forecast
of heavy snow fall this evening..
..we'll be closing
the shop in half an hour.
Listen, Madhu.
It was just announced that
there will be heavy snowfall here.
All roads will get blocked.
Raj will pick us up in some time.
You have to do one thing.
Did you understand
what you have to do?
Have you bought groceries
for the entire year?
Where is Priya?
Is she still shopping?
She left an hour ago. - What?
Doesn't she know there's going
to be a snow storm? - She knows.
She had to buy some things from
around the house. So she left.
She must have reached home by now.
- Come on, put the trolley there.
I'll do it.
From that side.
Hello.
Do you speak English? - Yes, sir.
Could you tell me if there
is an Indian girl in your store?
Her name is Priya.
Sorry, sir. The shop is closed.
There is no customer.
- All right. Thank you.
Welcome.
Madhu, the phone is ringing.
Hello. Yes, Priya.
Where are you?
In the church.
All right, stay there.
I'll pick you up.
How can you come? All roads are
blocked because of the snowfall.
Don't worry about me. There
are many people with me here.
I'll come as soon
as the road clears up.
You have blocked the roads.
You can say that.
If you two are not left alone,
how will we achieve our goal?
I love you.
I love you too.
Sorry. I mixed a little
vodka with the cold drink.
It's too cold outside.
That's why..
Madhu.
I love my wife very much.
I..
Congratulations. Good news.
She is expecting.
Congratulations.
Priya you have become a mother.
She has become mother.
Ten lakhs.
Ten lakhs?
Congrats, Raj. Congrats.
Bless daughter-in-law
in our behalf.
And look, come here on the
first available flight.
No, grandpa, this is not possible.
Because the doctor has prohibited
from talking long flights.
All right, don't come. Don't
come with daughter-in-law.
But take care of daughter-in-law
there.
What is happening there?
Take, talk with your mother.
Son Raj.
- Yes, mother.
Congrats. Live long. May
God give you my age.
Give the phone to daughter-in-law.
I won't.
- Give. - one second. - Hello.
Live long dear. Stay happy.
Don't pick up any heavy load.
Yes.
And the tie the sacred
thread I gave you.
Okay, mother.
Talk with father.
Hello.
Congratulations. No, do
as the doctor says.
All right.
- And take care of daughter-in-law.
Okay. - Okay, son bye. God
bless you. Bye. Bye. Bye.
Give me the phone.
- Congrats. - You hung up.
Madhu. Madhu.
- What is this?
It contains flowers
offered to God.
Mother has given them to me
for the baby's protection.
Always wear it. This will
protect the baby.
Priya.
- Yes.
Priya, it is 3 months. My belly
has not inflated till now.
Madhu the belly comes
out after 5, 6 months.
Even I was worried like you when
I was expecting last year.
Mother-in-law! They are
very dangerous, right?
No, my mother-in-law is not
like that. She is very nice.
She loves me a lot.
And Raj's grandpa.
He considers me his grand daughter
and not daughter-in-law.
Who else is there in your family?
There is a doctor grandpa
who is grandpa's friend.
There is an uncle and an aunt.
And Pappu brother.
His contacts are so bad that
if a phone develops trouble..
..he will all the telecom minister
instead of a mechanic.
And every new person thinks wrong
with his habit of winking.
You must be having great fun
in your in-laws house.
You might not know when
the day passes.
It was like that before.
But since I..
But those days will come
again thanks to you.
Congrats Raj, our company has
crossed the mark of 10 millions.
This is nothing it will cross
further 100 billion. - Yes.
Hi Ajay. - Hello, sister-in-law.
How are you? - I am fine.
This is my friend, Madhu.
- Hi. - And he is Ajay.
Raj's friend and business partner.
- Hello.
Thank you. Ladies and gentlemen.
Today I stand here
in front of you..
..to launch a new product
of my company, our company.
Its called cosmetics of India.
And the person who is
going to launch..
..this product for us today is a
very important part of my life.
Come Madhu.
Yes, Madhu. You are
our V.I.P. Come on.
Please come.
- Thanks. Thank you.
Hey Seth, come here.
Are you guys having a good time?
- Congrats.
Priya.
Raj, Vicky brother has arrived.
- Excuse me.
Congratulations Priya.
Congratulations.
Congratulations Raj.
- Thank you.
Brother,
sister-in-law has not come.
She is busy because it
is my son's shaving..
..ceremony the day after.
But I have come.
I have to come to invite on
my son's shaving ceremony.
Okay.
Hello. - Hi. - I was thinking
where I have seen you.
Strange. You have changed so much.
No one can see you and say
that you're a prostitute.
Who told you?
I and Raj never had any secrets.
Even I like good things.
If it is good I don't
care about money.
Come as soon as you
are over with Raj.
I will give you double the
money Raj is giving you.
Okay.
Excuse me, I will catch you later.
Why have you come here after
leaving the party?
I don't want to stay here.
I am going back.
Why what happened? Did anyone
tell you anything?
All you rich people are the same?
You play so many games
for your selfish means.
First you gave me so much respect.
And then you insulted me
so badly with one shock.
You needed a baby I could have
given birth one in the road.
What was the need to make
me suit your society?
When you had to tell your friends
that I am a prostitute.
I didn't feel so cheap when I used
to go whoring as I did today.
Did Ajay tell you anything?
Madhu, I have not told
anyone anything.
When you came to the Mumbai
conference that day..
Madhu.
Madhu, where are you going?
I am going back. He told
his friend that I am a..
That is am pregnant
and I can't dance.
Madhu, Raj and I are your
friends and well wishers.
We will never say anything
which will hurt you.
You want to dance. Come.
No, I don't want to dance.
Raj, human minds if someone whom..
..he regards to be close
says anything.
Priya, I have not told you
a thing about Madhu.
I know. I have heard everything.
You were right in not
telling me this before.
Maybe I wouldn't have accepted..
..Madhu then after knowing this.
But today I can say that Madhu
is best to mother our child.
Isn't it?
- Yes.
How is Madhu?
- I have just come from her room.
She is still angry.
She will feel very
bad if we 2 leave..
..her alone for the
shaving ceremony.
Then let's cancel the visit.
- No. Vicky brother will mind.
Let's do one thing. I will go
to the ceremony. You stay here.
And I will make the excuse that
you couldn't come due to work.
Yes, okay.
Go and pack your luggage.
I will drop you at
the station. Come.
Drink the juice.
Smoking is very good for your
and the baby's health.
Look, Madhu. I know you are upset.
But when you came to the
Munabi conference..
..in that dress and behaviour..
Ajay was there too.
Why will I tell this to Ajay when
I concealed it from my wife?
If you still think that I
am guilty then I am sorry.
Smoke.
Hi. Were you bathing?
- Raj is not at home.
He is at the office.
- Yes, I know he is at the office.
And is going to come late. And
even Priya is not at home.
She has gone to
her cousin's place.
That's why I have come.
I couldn't control since the time
I have seen you at the party.
That's why I came as soon
as I got the chance.
I have enjoyed every sort
girl in the world.
But no one has the thing you have.
Please go away from here.
Yes, I understood.
You are worried because you
are in Raj's contract.
We don't have any problem.
He is my business partner and
my childhood friend too.
He won't have any objection.
Let's not waste time now.
You lowly whore you slapped me.
Come on get up. Here.
You try to act decent.
I will take out your decency now.
Raj, I thought..
What did you think? That
you will rape her.
That you will rape her.
-What are you doing, Raj?
- Listen to me, Raj.
That you will rape her.
Raj! Raja. Raj, listen to me.
Raj, my..
Raj, what are you doing?
You are beating me for
this lowly prostitute.
You saw a prostitute in her.
I didn't see one.
How did you see? How did you see?
How did you see?
- Raj!
Raj, you are beating your
childhood friend for such a girl.
Childhood friend.
If you were even my brother, even
then I would have killed you.
Understand?
Raj, you are kicking your 500
crore partnership for her.
I will throw away the
entire wealth for her.
Understand?
Do you know why? Because
she is precious for me.
You are friend, right. That's
why leave from here.
Otherwise I will kill you.
Understand? Go.
Come. Come.
I will go get the medicines.
Call me if you
need anything, okay.
Hi!
This is for you.
Raj.
Madhu.
- Yes.
Take this.
What were you thinking?
I was remembering my childhood.
My mother used to tell me
takes when I was young.
There was poor girl.
One day a prince came to
her riding a white horse.
And took her away as his bride.
And then her dreams
were fulfilled.
Even I used to see this
dream all the time.
When I grew up, many white
cars came to me.
There were many princes
among them too.
But no one came to take
me. All came buy me.
Then I realised that that was
just a childhood fairy tale.
This doesn't happen in reality.
Thank you very much.
Raj and Priya will be
amazed to see us.
Chhotu,
unload the luggage quickly.
Bansi, how will carry
so much luggage alone?
Come with me.
Priya, grandpa has come with
the entire family. - What?
That is your family.
- Yes.
Priya, there will be trouble.
They think you are pregnant.
O God!
- One second.
No, this will be too big.
- This. - Yes, this is okay.
And listen you wear this amulet.
But the veneration
flowers are here.
Yes, I know it contains
veneration flowers.
You keep the veneration
flowers and you wear it.
Raj.
Daughter-in-law. We have arrived.
You will be very happy.
- Where are you?
Grandpa.
- Dear Raj. - Mother. Grandpa.
Live long. Live long.
- Dad. - How are you, son?
Good to see you. Good to see you.
- Mother.
Did we surprise you?
- Absolutely. - Live long, son.
This is not fair.
- Why? - You came without informing.
Surprise. - We cannot stay
without seeing Priya.
So we have come.
- But where is Priya.
Where is she? - She is tying the
pillow. - Tying the pillow?
Tying the pillow? What did you
hear? - What did you say?
She is changing.
Priya.
Come dear, come.
My child. Greetings, mamma.
Live long. You have given
me all happiness.
No, dear, don't bend. Live long.
- Greetings, father.
How are you?
- Live long.
Wait I will cast of your evil eye.
- Grandpa.
How are you, dear? - I am fine.
How are you Pappu brother?
How are you uncle?
- How are you Priya dear?
I told you if God wants you will
have a child within a year.
What mamma? You shouldn't have
surprised us like this?
You should have told us.
We would have come to fetch
you at the airport.
We wanted to but then father said
we shouldn't bother daughter-in-law.
There is nothing to bother here.
We have come to give a surprise.
What happened?
- What happened?
This is my friend's wife, Madhu.
Her husband generally stays
out because of business.
There is no one in her house
that's why she stays with us
All right.
That is good dear.
You shouldn't stay alone
at such times.
Come here. Come here.
Greetings.
- Stay happy. Live long.
I am Priya's mother-in-law.
- I know.
Priya tells me about you everyday.
You are aunt. You are uncle.
And you are Pappu brother.
And you are grandpa. Greetings.
Don't bend down. Live long,
dear. Live long.
And you are father. Greetings.
Grandpa. Won't you cast
away my evil eye?
Why not, dear? Live
long. Stay happy.
Always stay wedded.
It is not a laughing matter.
Why does Mithun Chakraborty
stay in Ooty?
So that he seems fairer
among the people there.
Grandpa biscuits.
- Thank you.
Madhu dear, what business
does your husband do?
Of import and export.
- Yes, grandpa.
That's why he is often in U.K.
Austria, Indonesia, Malaysia..
He always stays outside.
All right.
No matter what.
Business will go on.
But the husband should be with
his wife at such times.
No problem, daughter-in-law.
We will look after her the same
way we will look after Priya.
After hearing this Lord Vishnu
started crying as a child.
And seeing his cute from
mother Kaushalya..
..started shedding tears
of joy and affection.
It is said that if a pregnant
lady hears the description of..
..Lord Ram's birth then even
her unborn child enjoys it.
Feel and see.
Some movement must
be taking place.
Madhu dear. Why are
you standing there?
Come and sit here.
Come.
Sit. So listen.
How was father Dasrath during
Lord Ram's birth?
Because a father rejoices twice..
..over his baby's birth
than the mother.
What are you thinking, dear?
That your husband is not with you.
He might have some problem.
But he must be always thinking
about you and your baby.
So Tulsi Das said that Ram..
Priya. Dear Priya.
- Yes, mother.
These are special sweets.
Remember?
I have brought them
from Delhi for you.
Take eat it. Well done.
Come Madhu sister.
Mother has brought special
sweets for me from Delhi.
It will benefit you
if you eat it. Eat.
It is spicy right.
I used to find it spicy too when
I was expecting last year.
That's' why mother used to
force me into eating it.
Will you eat another?
- Madhu.
Mother is coming. Don't tell
her that you ate the sweet.
Madhu.
- Yes, mother. - You are here.
And I was looking for
you in your room.
I was sitting with Grandpa.
What is the matter?
You are crying.
No, I was watching a sentimental
movie that's why..
You cried. Come with me.
Come sit. Slowly.
Madhu dear these
are special sweets.
Both mother and baby benefit
by eating these.
Come on eat it.
- No, mother. I will eat them later.
No, not later. You will have
to eat them in front of me.
Otherwise you won't eat it.
I know it is a little spicy.
Come on open your mouth.
- No mother. Mother I..
Well done. Open your mouth.
Open your mouth. Well done.
Well done. It's okay,
right? Well done.
Madhu, your feet have swelled up.
I told him but
he said this happens.
It surely happens but too
much welling is not good.
I will apply the medicinal
oil in your feet.
Swelling will stop by that.
Bansi, bring that medicinal oil.
Place it here.
- Yes. - Come dear. - No, mother.
I won't like you to touch my feet.
- But I will like it.
The one whom I have called
daughter is a daughter to me.
You are my daughter, right?
Who are there in your
family, daughter?
I don't have anyone, mother.
There must be someone in India.
They are not in this world.
In future never say
that you have no one.
From now this entire
family is yours.
Hello. Greetings priest. How
are you? Yes, one minute.
Grandpa. - Yes, dear. - Priest
has called from Delhi.
Hello. Yes priest. Greetings.
- Whose call is it? - Priest's.
What is he saying?
- I don't know. - All right.
We will do as you say. You
start the preparations.
What preparations grandpa?
Raj, priest has fixed the 18th
for Priya's baby shower.
Congratulations. We will go
to Delhi tomorrow. All right.
Ranjeet. Daughter-in-law.
Raj, how can we return to India?
Madhu should be with us too.
Because Priya's baby shower
has been fixed for the 18th.
Come.
Go to the office with Raj and call a
board meeting to explain everybody.
Yes, father. - Grandpa, can't
you call the priest here.
And have the baby shower here.
- Why?
Because Priya's delivery
date is due this month.
And the medical facilities
are good here.
Don't talk about facilities.
I will make a call and transfer
all facilities to Delhi.
What is the phone number of
the facility minister here?
There is no facility of
ministers here. - Is it?
Bihar is better than this place.
Son Raj we will find all medical
facilities in Delhi.
And baby shower is done where
you have friends and relatives.
You are right, mother. We
all will go to India.
Madhu, I had promised your husband
that I will look after you.
Because your and Priya's delivery
date is on the same day.
But all of us are going to
India for the baby shower.
And I can never refuse grandpa.
But I will do all your
hospital bookings.
And go whenever you have
the labour pains.
Manage that, please.
- Have you gone crazy?
How can she go alone to the
hospital at such conditions?
Grandpa she has no other way out.
Who is there with her?
And she cannot even come to
India with us. - Why not?
You had promised
her husband, right?
Yes, I had. - All of you listen.
This is my decision.
That Madhu will come
with us to Delhi.
Why dear? Do you have
any objections? - No.
Hi.
Come, brother.
- Greetings.
That is my papa and those are
my brother and sister-in-law.
What have they brought?
- Gifts.
The pregnant mother wears
clothes gifted..
..by her family during
the baby shower.
This is very big occasion.
Greetings.
- Come. Come. - Come. Come. -Come.
Pappu, listen.
- Yes.
The priest is asking for
rice. Arrange for it.
Shall I call the food minister?
How many sacks do you want?
You will call the minister
for a fistful of rice.
Bring from the kitchen.
- A fistful. - Okay. - Come.
Excuse me.
- Yes.
Have you see Bhatia uncle,
anywhere?
I didn't see him. But
what is the matter?
Are you copying me?
No, this is my childhood habit.
Did you mother go to the
red bungalow in Fatehpur.
My mother has never gone to
the red bungalow in Fatehpur.
My father used to go their often.
Father always used to say that
you have a sister. Father.
Priya your gift dress has arrived.
Now get ready quickly.
- Mother, go downstairs.
I will prepare
Priya and bring her.
No, dear. You cannot
come downstairs.
Look dear even I wanted to have
your baby shower with Priya.
But the priest said that
2 pregnant ladies..
..cannot attend this
function together.
All right, mother.
And dear Priya. Decorate yourself
like a bride today.
Yes. - Baby shower is a big
occasion in a woman's life.
Because a woman has
not 1 but 3 births.
First when she comes to this
world as someone's daughter.
2nd when she becomes
someone's wife.
And 3rd when she becomes a mother.
And baby shower is being done
before becoming a mother..
..so that the baby to be born
is blessed with happiness.
Now get ready quickly. It is
time for the shower, dear.
Raj, you here. Don't engage
Priya in talks now.
She has to get ready and come
downstairs, okay. - Yes.
Raj, I cannot go to this function.
- Why?
Mother said it is
no ordinary custom.
This veneration and prayers are
being made to bless our child.
Madhu should attend this
shower instead of me.
But how is that possible?
If Madhu wears my wedding dress
then there will be a veil.
And nobody will know
that she is Madhu.
Please Raj.
Madhu, will you wear
this gift dress?
All right.
Thank you.
Sister-in-law- Yes. - go and
see if Priya is ready.
Go and bring her. Hurry up.
- Okay. - Aunt.
I will go and see. Mother,
I will bring her.
Look. All right, you
go and bring her.
Who is it?
- Me.
Is Madhu ready?
- Yes, she is. - Oh my god. Girls.
Hey, I forgot the sacred thread..
- Listen.
I will make her wear it. You go.
- Okay, I will go that side.
Priya. Priya. Come here.
The one who will give my family
my heir, I salute you.
May God let our
child live for eras.
And your child should spread
my family's name like sun.
Let God add my age to your child.
He should bring incomparable
happiness to your life.
Priya, you have got such a dark
henna colour in your hands.
This means Raj loves you a lot.
We have to take a family
photograph. Come.
Come. Come. Come.
- Yes.
Come. Come.
- Come Raj dear.
Yes, take a photograph.
"Henna."
- Priest, start the veneration.
Tell the baby's grandfather.
Lala Kailash Nath Malhotra.
Lala Kailash Nath Malhotra's
great grandson is arriving.
The entire clan should benefit.
The Baby's grandfather's name.
Ranjeet Kumar Malhotra.
Ranjeet Kumar Malhotra grandson
should get all success.
The baby grandma's name.
- Asha Malhotra.
Asha Malhotra's grandson
should live long.
The baby's father's name.
Raj Malhotra.
Raj Malhotra should live long.
The baby's mother's name.
Priya Malhotra.
Mother.
The function was great today.
- Very nice.
The best was father's dance.
What do you have to say?
What a storm? I will have
the windows closes.
It is late now. You go and
sleep too. - Okay, mother.
Sleep tight. Live long.
Bansi!
Madhu.
Have you seen Madhu anywhere?
Yes, she has just left towards
the station. - What?
Madhu.
Where are you going?
Priya Malhotra is not the mother
of this baby. It is me.
This is my baby. I
won't give my baby.
Forgive me.
I can't give this baby.
Madhu, don't say like this.
I have done penance for 9 months
for the baby's birth.
We have dreamt for this
baby every day.
This time not only
me and Raj, but..
..our entire family is waiting
for this baby's birth.
Our happiness is connected
to it, Madhu.
I will die,
but won't give my baby.
Madhu, you don't have anything
lacking like me.
You can get married. You
can be a mother again.
But I am not complete. I
can never be a mother.
Madhu, I pray give me this baby.
I will give you whatever you
want for it. Money, property.
Madhu, tell me what do you need?
All right, I am ready
to give you my baby.
Can you give me your husband?
At last you have shown
me your reality.
I though even
prostitutes are woman.
But a prostitute can
do no good to others.
She can only break homes.
I asked you your husband and
you reminded me my reality.
You are asking a mother her child.
A mother is mother whether she is
a prostitute or a daughter-in-law.
I won't give you my baby.
I won't give you my baby. My baby.
Raj. Raj. She is refusing
to give our baby.
Priya, first look at
her condition. Madhu. Madhu.
Madhu. Madhu. Madhu. Call
doctor grandpa immediately.
Don't worry. Everything
will be fine.
We are scanning Madhu.
We will get to know the
complications soon.
Mother is calling. Yes, mother.
You, Priya and Madhu are not
at home. Where are you?
Mother we are at the hospital.
Madhu and Priya's labour
pain has started.
So I brought them here.
What? I will give this
good news to everyone.
We are reaching the hospital. Okay.
- No, mother. No.
You can come later. Okay.
Doctor grandpa is with me.
I am just coming.
Excuse me.
The doctor has called you inside.
Come.
The baby has turned that's why it
is not in its normal position.
We have to operate
her immediately.
All right, go ahead.
- But the condition is serious.
I can save either the mother
or baby in this operation.
We have to decide quickly.
Doctor, save the mother.
Prepare her to be taken to the
operation theatre. - Yes.
Nurse, take Mr. Raj's signature.
- All right.
Come on, nurse. Take
her inside. Careful.
Good news. This happens
in rare cases.
The operation was successful.
Both the baby and Madhu are safe.
Congratulations, you had a son.
What ac cute baby.
You wanted to save
the mother, right?
The mother is saved
and even your baby.
I was moved a bit for a while.
I became selfish.
You are the mother of this baby.
He is yours.
Give me my great grandson.
Look. Look.
- SO sweet. So sweet.
I am your great grandpa.
- Give him to me, please.
Yes, what did our Madhu
have? Boy or girl?
That poor girl lost
her child at birth..
No dear,
don't dishearten yourself.
Think that it was not yours.
The same had happened
to our Priya too.
But see, God had made
her a mother in a year.
Yes, dear.
Don't go, Madhu. I will tell
the family members the truth.
If 2 brothers can stay together
then why not 2 sisters?
I have got an entire family here.
I only lacked a sister.
I have found her too, today.
Let this sister remain a sister.
Don't make her your co-wife.
Otherwise no woman will
trust another woman.
Only you have the right
on this family and Raj.
My rights are on the
memories I got here.
I became a daughter here,
a bride and a mother.
What else do I want?
Madhu, I have checked you on.
This is your boarding pass.
I have deposited your
bags in the luggage.
This contains the keys
to your new house.
And some blank cheques
with your name.
My entire wealth is less for what
you did for me and Priya.
Just consider this to be a small
gift from me and Priya.
I have taken the gift. See this.
I am taking me entire
family with me.
If I take anything more than
that then I will feel..
..that a mother has taken
the price of her baby.
But Madhu you..
I won't return to that world
from where you brought me.
You have touched me once.
Now no one else can touch me.
Thank you.